饥饿
的青春
第二季  第十五集
0,0,0,fx,学习
0,0,0,fx,分享
0,0,0,fx,进步
本字幕由ZiMuZu原创翻译
最新下载请登录www.ZiMuZu.tv
翻译   冰蓝     aaaBao
翻译  roaddog
校对  roaddog
时间轴 aaaBao
后期 斯人       总监 roaddog
打开微信   扫描左侧二维码
或搜索公众号:    ustvboom
了解最新影视字幕发布信息
好了  幸运饼干时间
Okay. Fortune cookie time.
选一个
Pick one.
这个  不  这个
This one. No, this one.
-不  这个  -这个怎么样
- No, this one. - Okay, how about this one?
"别人求助时  你很乐意竭尽全力"
"When asked, you will gladly bend over backwards."
无聊
Boring!
是啊  它们都好无聊
Yeah, they're all boring.
所以你得加上"在床上"
That's why you have to add "in bed."
"别人求助时  你很乐意在床上竭尽全力"
"When asked, you will gladly bend over backwards..." in bed!
-真棒  轮到你了  -好好好
- That's good. Okay. Your turn. Your turn. - Okay. Okay. Okay.
拜托告诉我我能找到工作
Oh, please tell me I'm going to get a job.
什么  开玩笑吗
What? Are you kidding me?
我什么都没有
I got nothing.
在床上
In bed!
不  我真的什么都没有  我饼干是空的
No. I really don't have anything. My cookie's empty.
在床上
In bed!
加比  行了  我真的很沮丧
Gabi, stop. I'm really depressed.
显然我永远也找不到工作了
It's obvious I'm never going to get a job
连饼干都没胆子告诉我
and this cookie doesn't have the balls to tell me.
坐在家里掰幸运饼干
Okay. Well, you're never going to get a job
是找不到工作的  好吗
sitting at home reading fortune cookies. Okay?
你得严肃对待
You have to take this seriously.
得去真正能
You have to go somewhere
帮你找到工作的地方
that actually is going to help you find a job.
那是哪里
And where is that?
精灵告诉我
The spirits are telling me
你就快有钱了
that money is coming your way.
好吧  这跟幸运饼干有什么区别
Okay. How is this different from a fortune cookie?
她不是饼干
Well, she's not a cookie,
是训练有素的专业人士
and she is a trained professional.
这太荒唐了
This is ridiculous.
我看到你很快就会...
I see that soon you will be--
退我钱  在床上
asking for a refund "in bed."
难以置信你居然带我来这里
I can't believe you brought me here.
我该带你去哪里啊
Well, where was I supposed to bring you?
不知道  去找求职顾问啊
I don't know. A job counselor?
求职顾问
A job counselor.
好像那不骗人一样
Like that's not a total scam!
我感受到了紧张
I'm sensing tension.
瞧见没  她很厉害
See? She's good.
好吧
Okay. Yeah, okay.
拥有看出面部表情基本技能的陌生人
Absolute stranger with rudimentary skills at reading facial cues,
跟我说说我的"未来"
tell me my "future."
我感应到了
Ooh, I'm getting something.
我感受到了你俩的生活
I sense that both of your lives
都要动摇了
are about to be shaken up.
天啊
Oh, my god.
太含糊了吧
That's super vague.
还有更多
There's more.
你们将会遭遇地震
There's going to be a seismic shift in your world.
天啊
Oh, my god.
你说的内容完全一样
You just said the same thing...
只不过这次是轻声说的
but you whispered it.
震动会传播...
The tremors are gonna ripple through--
现在你只是在用不同的词汇
Now you're just using different words.
地震  贱人
Earthquake, bitch!
会有地震
There's going to be an earthquake!
瞧瞧你做的事
See? See what you did.
你让她生气了  现在会有一场地震了
You made her mad and now there's going to be an earthquake.
加比  拜托  谁都能预测地震
Gabi, come on. Anyone can predict an earthquake.
这可是旧金山
This is San Francisco.
但她没说到底是什么时候
But she didn't say exactly when it was gonna happen.
你下次尿尿的时候就会地震
It's gonna happen the next time you pee.
我吗
Me?
索菲亚  你能不能把蛋糕样品
Sofia, could you take the cake samples
端过去  我动不了
over to the table, please? I can't move.
加比  这样不健康  去尿尿好吗
Gabi, this is not healthy. Would you just pee already?
旧金山的命运
The fate of San Francisco
取决于我的膀胱
rests on my bladder.
你太可笑了
You are being ridiculous.
我可不觉得这种情况好笑
Oh, I don't think anything about this situation is ridiculous.
天啊
Oh, my god.
我们的婚礼蛋糕必须是这个黑巧克力甘那许蛋糕
Our wedding cake has to be this dark chocolate ganache.
这是我的一号选择
It's my number one choice.
请不要说"一号"
Please don't say "Number one."
但我喜欢花生酱的
But I like the peanut butter.
请不要说"哗"
Please don't say pee.
好  够了
Okay, that's enough.
过来  我得告诉你一件事
Come over here. I gotta tell you something.
不不不
No, no, no, no, no.
索菲亚  干嘛  我在试吃蛋糕
Sofia, what, okay? I'm doing cake tasting--
棒
Yes!
不
Oh, no!
大家快找掩护
Take cover, everybody!
天啊  她到底有多迫切
Damn, how bad does she have to go?
索菲亚  怎么回事
Sofia, what's going on?
加比觉得如果她尿尿  就会发生...
Gabi thinks that if she pees there's going to be an--
地震了
Earthquake!
你们感受到了吗  大家都还好吗
Did you guys feel that? Is everybody okay?
摔坏[破戒]什么了吗
Did anything break?
有  我的减肥大计
Yeah. My diet.
非常感谢你让我们插队
Thank you so much for squeezing us in.
是的  抱歉之前的质疑  你拥有大智慧
Yes, I am so sorry that I ever doubted you. Ye have much wisdom.
能告诉我们将会发生的一切吗
Can you tell us everything that's going to happen?
对  千万别漏了什么细节  好吗
Yeah. Don't leave anything out, okay?
首先  尿尿没什么影响了吧
And first off, is it safe to pee again?
这是什么意思
What does that mean?
我的微波爆米花好了
My microwave popcorn is done.
我看到了
Yes!
你会得到一大笔钱...
You're going to be offered a big bundle of money...
这钱会给你
...which will lead to you
带来个蓝布包裹的大胖小子
having a big chubby bundle of joy wrapped in blue.
一大笔钱...你就要找到工作了
A bundle of money-- you're going to get a job!
是啊  并且新同事会让我怀孕
Yeah. And some guy at my new job is going to knock me up.
等等  什么
Wait. What?
出于本能  你会对这件事说不  但别这么做
Your instinct will be to say no to this offer, but don't.
她不会的  现在说说我吧
Oh, she won't. Now me.
我看到有人会要你伸出手
I see that someone is going to ask for your hand.
我的手  就像求婚那样吗
My hand? Like in marriage?
这不清楚
It's unclear.
但这段感情会"性感的冒烟"
But something about this relationship is gonna be smoking hot.
那人是谁  告诉我
Who is it? Tell me!
能透露一点给我吗
Can you tell me anything? Something?
他的名字是字母J开头的
Well, his name starts with the letter "J."
J吗
"J"?
谁的名字是字母J开头的
Whose name starts with the letter "J"?
J...  J...
"J"..."J"...
第二个字母是不是O
Is the second letter "O"?
是不是O
贱人  不能问元音字母
Bitch, you can't buy a vowel.
这又不是《幸运之轮》
This isn't Wheel of Fortune.
电视猜字游戏节目
你以为我是谁  凡娜·怀特[节目主持人]吗
Who do I look like, Vanna White?
乔什  你没事吧
Josh, you okay?
上次我见到一个男人如此费劲地呼吸时...
Last time I saw a man struggling that hard to breathe...
我们只好互换体位
we had to switch positions.
我没事
I'm okay.
我只是...刚刚爬了27层楼梯  我没事
I just...walked up 27 flights of stairs. I'm okay.
可是地震后他们已经修好电梯了
But they fixed the elevator after the earthquake.
你没听说过余震吗
You ever heard of aftershocks?
我小时候  发生过一次地震
When I was a kid, there was an earthquake,
我独自一人在电梯里被困了两个小时
I was trapped alone in this elevator for two hours.
到现在  我听到轻爵士的时候还会抖
To this day I shudder whenever I hear light jazz.
我也是
Yeah. Me, too.
白人毁一切
White people ruin everything.
爵士乐为黑人首创
该死  我忘拿手机了
Oh, damn it. I left my phone down there.
尤兰达  你介意...
Hey, Yolanda, would you mind--
突发新闻
Newsflash!
乔什  黑人女性打开有钱白人的车
Josh, a black woman going to a rich white man's car,
拿走他的手机...
taking his phone...
不会有好下场的
never ends well.
现在我希望你  走出房门
Now, what I want you to do, is I want you to go out there,
步入电梯  让它知道谁厉害
get in that elevator and show it who's boss.
你说得对  是我太神经质
You're right. I'm being crazy.
-没错  -乔什·卡明斯基
- Hell, yeah, you are! - Josh Kaminski!
-战胜它  卡明斯基  -我什么都不怕
- Kick ass, Kaminski! - I'm not scared of stuff!
没错  你不怕
Damn straight, you're not.
我想坐就能坐
I can take it if I feel like it.
但我不想坐
But I don't feel like it.
真不敢相信乔什会向我求婚
I can't believe Josh is going to propose to me.
他怎么想的
What is he thinking?
我们连恋爱都没谈成...
I mean, we couldn't make dating work...
怎么就会结得成婚呢
How are we supposed to make marriage work?
他疯了吧
He is out of his mind.
至少你会得到一枚戒指...
At least you're getting a ring...
我将成为你未婚先孕的好朋友
I'm going to be the unmarried pregnant best friend.
我一直以为那会是你
I always thought that would be you.
我在这个男人手下工作
I mean, I work for the man.
他会让我处于一个非常尴尬的境地
He's putting me in a very awkward position.
你想聊聊尴尬处境吗
Oh, you want to talk about awkward position?
试想一下妊娠末期了
Try being in your third trimester
还在"愿者上钩"上面寻找另一半
and looking for a date on Tinder.
好吧  我们得互相支持  好吗
Okay. Well, we just have to stick together, okay?
你陪着我  别让乔什向我求婚
You stay by my side and don't let Josh propose to me.
好  同时你陪着我
Okay. And you stay by my side
别让任何人搞大索小姐的肚子
and don't let anyone put a baby in Lil' So-so.
两位  你们在干吗
Hey, guys, what you doing?
加比  我知道这事对你非常陌生...
Gabi, I know this is unfamiliar to you...
但我们管这叫阅读
But it's called reading.
这是生育诊所里的小册子
It's a pamphlet on fertility.
经历了这场可怕的地震之后...
After that dreadful earthquake...
我们意识到生命短暂
We realized life is short.
所以我们聊起了人生  并且...
So we started talking about life, and we--
决定要个孩子
Decided to have a baby!
你想告诉她们吗  说吧
Oh, you wanted to tell them? Go ahead.
我们决定生个孩子  算了
We decided to have a baby. Whatever--
-恭喜  -太棒了
- Congratulations! - Oh, guys, that's amazing!
因此我们很高兴见到你俩
That's why we're so glad to see you.
用匿名捐赠者的卵子太不近人情了
Using an anonymous egg donor is so impersonal.
所以我们想在认识的人里找
So we'd rather ask someone we know.
你愿意当我们的卵子捐赠人吗  索菲亚
Would you consider being our egg donor, Sofia?
你想问她吗  问吧
Oh, do you want to ask her? Go ahead.
你愿意当...  算了
Would you consider being-- ah, forget it.
天呐
Oh, my God!
等等  你们想用她的卵子吗
Wait, you want one of her eggs?
不是针对你  小加加
Oh, it's nothing personal, Gabalah.
我们只是不想养个熊孩子
We just don't want to raise a demon spawn.
我们会给你两万块补偿
We'd give you $20,000 for your egg
感谢你给我们的大胖小子
and you'd help us get a little bundle of joy.
-天啊  大胖小子  -老天
- Oh, my god, a bundle of joy! - Oh, my god!
还有一大笔钱
A bundle of money!
是真的
It's happening.
-你不用着急答应  -好的
- You don't have to say yes right now-- - Yes.
我就知道价开高了
I knew it. We started too high.
我说了八千她也会同意吧
I told you she would've taken eight.
那你明天能跟我们
So you'll go with us tomorrow
一起去看产科医生  检测一下吗
to a fertility doctor to see if you're a candidate?
灵媒让我要说"好"  所以没问题
Well, a psychic told me to say "Yes," so yes!
灵媒啊  我以为你说她聪明呢
A psychic! I thought you said she was smart.
等等  你的预言成真了
Wait, your prediction came true.
这是说明乔什就要...
Does that mean that Josh is about to--
加比
Gabi--
加比  你能...
Gabi, will you--
不不不  我还太年轻
No, no, no, no! I'm too young.
帮我做杯沙冰吗
Please make me a smoothie.
帮我做杯沙冰
Please make me a smoothie!
我知道这可能有点吓人  索菲亚
I know this might seem a little scary, Sofia...
但艾略特和我会一直陪着你的
but Elliot and I are here for you every step of the way.
有任何需要  就告诉我们
Anything you need, you let us know.
谢谢你们
Thanks, guys.
想想我们自己的大胖...
Just think, our own little bundle of--
糟糕
Crap!
看看这些海报
Look at all these posters.
不敢看
Oh, I can't!
多亏我已经弯了
If I wasn't gay already...
我真不知道该拿这东西怎么办
I wouldn't know the first thing to do with this.
是啊  直男也不知道
Yeah, neither do straight guys.
这里怎么会有电动牙刷
Why is there a sonicare in here?
那不是牙刷  是超声波探测棒
That's not a toothbrush. That's an ultrasound wand.
医生用它伸进...
Yeah, the doctors use it to look inside your--
丁丁  丁丁  丁丁
Penis! Penis! Penis! Penis!
这里还真全是那个道哈
It's all vagina all the time in here.
记得我们说要陪着你...
Remember that stuff we said about us being there--
-你们走吧  -我走了
- Yeah, just go. - I'm going to go.
开会愉快  乔什
Have a good meeting, Josh.
好  再见
Okay. See you.
-好的  -再见
- All right. - Bye!
想走楼梯吗
Trying to take the stairs?
楼梯门为什么锁了  着火怎么办
Why are these stair doors locked? It's a fire hazard.
因为我们正在帮你克服恐惧
Because we are conquering your fear right here and right now.
不
No!
这主意不好
That is a bad idea.
我不听你的
I don't wanna.
乔什  别担心  我上网查过了
Come on, Josh. Don't worry. I did a little research online.
说如果你想克服恐惧
And they say if you want to conquer your fear,
只要边干喜欢的事
all you have to do is
边经历恐惧环境就好
associate it with something that makes you happy.
比如开除你吗
Like firing you?
或者...
Or...
吃甜甜圈
donuts!
你一跨进电梯
Start eating one of these
就开始吃甜甜圈  像这样
as soon as you get on the elevator. Like this.
真好吃
Damn, that's good.
尤兰达  电梯门还没开呢
Yolanda, the elevator doors didn't even open.
是  但我嘴张开了
No. But my mouth did.
乔什
Josh!
进电梯去
Get in that elevator!
再见
Bye!
好吧  我能做到的
Okay. I can do this.
好吧  乔什
Yeah, okay, Josh.
说实话  我知道你要干什么
Honestly, I know what you're about to do
但我还没准备好
and I am just not ready.
我能看出你也很紧张
I can see that you're really nervous, too.
很好很好  没事的
It's going to be fine! It's going to be fine!
是啊  当然很好
Well, yeah, of course it's going to be fine.
你聪明又帅气
I mean, you're smart and you're handsome--
不  别这样  好吗
No, no, no, no. Don't do this, okay?
别跪...
Don't do--
是大震  是大震
It's a big one! It's a big one!
-怎么回事  -地震了
- What's happening? - Earthquake!
天啊  乔什  我嫁给你
Oh, god, Josh. I will marry you!
艾略特  震完了  放开我吧
Elliot, it's over. You can let go now.
但你好强壮
But you're so strong...
像是犹太版的钱宁·塔图姆
Like a Jewish Channing Tatum.
允许你再多抱五秒钟
You just bought yourself five more seconds.
天啊
God!
有人吗
Hello!
快来人救救我
Somebody! Somebody help!
索菲亚·玛利亚·康斯薇拉·拉斐尔·罗德里格斯
Sofia Maria Consuela Rafaella Rodriguez?
是我  等等  谁在喊我
That's me! Wait, who is that?
是上帝吗
Is that god?
差不多  我是沃克医生
Close. It's Dr. Walker
在尿样窗口这里
At the urine sample pass-through.
你还好吗
Are you okay?
不好  我打不开门
No! I can't get the door open.
别担心  我已经呼救了
Okay, don't worry. I already called for help.
会没事的
Everything's going to be fine.
说得容易  你反正在外面
That's easy for you to say. You're out there.
没错  如果我被困在里面  会慌死的
That's true. If I was trapped in there I'd be freaking out.
你能一直跟我聊天吗
Can you just keep talking to me?
我怕还会有余震
I'm scared there's going to be an aftershock.
好  你最喜欢什么味道的冰淇淋
Oh, okay. Um, what's your favorite ice cream?
巧克力蛋糕味  曲奇味  我还年轻不能死
Rocky road, cookie dough, too young to die.
最后那个不是味道  是我的感受
That last one's not a flavor, it's just how I feel.
天啊  我好害怕  你能说些别吗
Oh, my god. I'm freaking out. Can you just say something else?
你眼睛很漂亮
You have the prettiest eyes
是我从尿样窗口看过最美的
I've ever seen through a urine pass-through.
来的时候  我真没想过
Well, my eyes are not what I thought
你们会看的是我眼睛
you'd be looking into when I got here.
我们被困了吗
Are we stuck?
该怎么办
What're we gonna do?
首先让我把你放下来
Well, first I'm going to put you down.
好
'kay.
然后请解释下你为什么说要嫁给我
Then you're going to explain why you said you'll marry me.
好
'kay.
这个嘛
So--
你也知道的
you know that thing
就是那种觉得有人要跟你求婚了
where you think somebody's going to propose to you...
但你还没准备好  就说"不行"
but you're not ready, so you're like, "No way!"
然后你觉得自己要死了
and then you think you're going to die,
又说"我们结婚吧"的事情嘛
so you're like, "Let's do this!"
加比  你为什么会觉得
Gabi, what reason could you possibly have to think
我要向你求婚
I was going to propose to you?
-灵媒说的  -这就是了
- A psychic told me. - And there it is.
波莱特夫人说
Madame Paulette said,
有个名字是J开头的男人
the guy whose name started with the letter "J"
会让我伸出手
was going to ask for my hand
我们的关系会"性感的冒烟"
and that our relationship would be "smoking hot"!
这样哈
Well, I mean...
那的确是像我
that does sound like me.
就算波莱特夫人算的这么准
All right, look. As reliable of a source as Madame Paulette is...
但我向你保证  加比
I can assure you, Gabi,
我现在最不会干的  就是跟你求婚
the last thing I'm going to do right now is propose to you.
说"最不会"有点伤人吧
Yeah. The "last thing" is a little harsh.
讨厌的灵媒  她要是说了我们
Stupid psychic. It would've been nice if she was going to tell me
会被困在电梯里该多好
we're going to get stuck in an elevator.
根本不准
She sucks.
现在我们没事了吗
We're good now?
有事  我们还困在电梯里
No! We're stuck in an elevator!
放松  都会没事的
Okay, relax. Everything's going to be fine.
深呼吸
Take a deep breath. Breathe.
你看
See!
氧气还挺充足
Lot's of oxygen in here.
想活动的话  空间也很大
Plenty of space to move around if we want to.
或者原地不动
Or freeze exactly in place.
我得从这出去
I gotta get the hell outta here!
等等  你要干什么
What are you doing? Wait! What are you doing?
我要往上爬一层楼
I'm going to go climb up a floor
打开电梯门  找人来救你
and open the elevator doors, and get you help!
不  别这么做
No, no, no! Please don't go.
加比  我必须要在萨克斯独奏前出去
Gabi, I have to get out of here before the sax solo kicks in.
我能告诉你件事吗
Can I tell you something?
第一次地震以后  我在想
After the first earthquake, I was thinking
"人生苦短  赶快要个孩子吧"
"Life is short... why wait to have a kid?"
但现在我想
But now I'm thinking,
"人生苦短  何必浪费在孩子身上"
"Life is short... why spend it with a kid?"
真的吗
Really?
因为我以为我快死的时候
Because when I thought I was going to die,
心里没想孩子
I wasn't thinking about babies,
想的是你
I was thinking about you.
我们或许没多少日子了
We may not have that much time left,
但我知道剩下的我只想和你一起过
but I know I want to spend it with only you.
当然不是在这妇科中心
And not here in vagina central.
我的小犹太馅饼
Aw, my little knish!
我的小酸甜饺子
Aw! My little sweet and sour dumpling.
我突然饿了
Ooh, all of a sudden I'm hungry.
我可以去吃点东西
I could go for a nosh.
索菲亚怎么办
Oh, what about Sofia?
对啊  索菲亚
Oh, yeah! Sofia!
索菲亚  要我们给你带点东西吃吗
Sofia, you want anything from the deli?
我被困住了
I'm trapped in here!
那就是不要咯
We'll take that as a no.
我们会是好家长的
We would've made such good parents.
最好的
The best.
你愿意捐献卵子帮助朋友  真是心善
It's nice of you to consider donating an egg to help your friends.
说不上是捐献
Yeah, well, I'm not exactly donating.
这样做也有些是为了钱
I'm kinda doing it for the money.
还有是因为灵媒让我做的
And 'cause a psychic told me to.
灵媒说的  那当然要听了
Oh, a psychic. Well, then for sure you should do this.
你也觉得吗
You think?
不  神经病才听
No! It's crazy!
是吧  一开始我觉得
Isn't it? I mean, at first I thought,
"这钱来得容易  疼都不疼"
"Cha-ching, easy money and it wouldn't even hurt,"
然后又想"我的卵子会去哪里"
And then it's like, "Where'd my egg go?
"什么卵子  谁在乎
"What egg? Who cares?
我这还多着呢  根本不会想它"
I have a million more. I won't even miss it."
但又想  如果十八年后有人来敲我门
But then, what if in 18 years I get a knock on the door
开门是个孩子
and it's some kid saying,
喊我妈妈  我又说
"Mama," And then I'm like,
"菲德里克·何塞·巴勃罗·安立奎·罗德里格斯
"Federico Jose Pablo Enrique Rodriguez...
你怎么会在这"
What are you doing here?"
我能给你些建议吗
Can I give you some advice?
什么  来自专业人士的建议吗
What? Advice from an actual professional?
我洗耳恭听
That'll be a welcome change.
如果你还没准备好  就别做
If you're not ready for this, don't do it.
遵从你的内心
Follow your gut.
内心告诉我不要做
My gut is telling me to say no...
但银行账户对我说  "拿钱啊  傻瓜"
but my bank account is telling me, "take the money, fool."
我有个预言给你
Hey! I have a prediction for you.
什么
What?
一个年轻的单身医生会约你出去吃冰淇淋
A single, young doctor is going to ask you out for ice cream...
如果你不觉得他莽撞  又没乳糖不耐的话
if that's not too forward and you're not lactose intolerant?
我觉得我会高兴地答应
Uh, I think I'd really like that.
天啊  天啊
My god! Oh, my god!
我得救了
I'm saved!
我们外面见
I'll see you on the other side.
不管发生什么  我都会找到你
No matter what occurs, I will find you!
谢谢
Thank you!
索菲亚
Sofia?
是我  尿样窗口那个人
It's me, from the urine pass-through.
-天啊  -怎么了
- Oh, my god. - What?
灵媒说得对
The psychic was right.
不是孩子
It's not a baby at all.
你才是蓝布裹着的大胖小子
You're the chubby bundle of joy wrapped in blue.
还有人说过更难听的
I've been called worse.
你要是改主意了  我理解
But I get it if you changed your mind.
如果你不想去吃冰淇淋了  没关系
If you don't want to go out for ice cream. It's totally cool.
是啊  对不起
Oh, yeah, I'm sorry, I don't.
除非是吃完浪漫晚餐以后
Unless it's after a romantic dinner.
晚餐加冰淇淋吗
Dinner and ice cream?
真是完美之夜  你不去我都愿意
That's the perfect night. I don't even need you to go!
加比
Gabi!
是这层吗  我找到个消防员
Is this the right floor? I found a fireman.
是的  就是这层
Yes, yes, yes! This is the right floor.
谢天谢地  简直过了一辈子
Thank god, it's been forever!
才八分钟
It's been eight minutes.
-你还好吗  -我没事  快救我出去
- Are you okay? - Yeah, I'm fine. Just get me out of here.
把手给我
Give me your hand.
抱歉  你说什么
I'm sorry, what did you say?
手  把你的手给我
Your hand. Give me your hand.
你想让我伸出手吗
You're asking me for my hand?
是的  我好拉你出来
Yeah, so I can pull you out of there.
你叫什么
What's your name?
-雷诺兹副队  -名字  不是姓
- Lieutenant Reynolds. - First name. First name.
-杰森  -杰森吗
- Jason. - Jason!
J开头的吗
With a "J"?
女士  你在里面撞到头了吗
Ma'am, did you hit your head in there?
没有  我没事  灵媒说得好对
No, no! I'm fine. Oh, my god, the psychic was right!
一个J开头的人真的要我伸手
A "J" did ask for my hand.
而且还"性感的冒烟"
And she was right about smoking hot!
谢谢
Thank you.
我重点在"冒烟"  不过你好  我叫加比
Well, I meant 'cause you're a fireman, but hi, I'm Gabi.
我还要去别的楼层搜救
Well, I have to see about the people in the other floors...
不过你要愿意  我等下再来看你
but I can check on you later if you want.
好  我愿意
Yeah, I want.
我在顶楼上班  有时间来玩
I work in the penthouse. Swing by anytime.
好  等会见
All right. Well, I'll see you guys later.
都等不及了
Looking forward to it.
他好勇敢
He is so brave.
我从电梯里挤出来
I shimmied out of the elevator...
沿着钢缆爬上去
climbed up the cable...
徒手撬开楼上的电梯门
pried the doors open above us with my bare hands...
找到人来救你  是啊
and I found you help, but yeah...
他才了不起
he's superman.
我们不住这层
And this is not our floor.
波莱特夫人
Madame Paulette...
我一般都去找自由大街的斯嘉丽算命
I usually talk to my girl Scarlet over on Liberty Street...
但我两个朋友来你这以后都找到了对象
but both my friends said they met guys after seeing you.
希望我也能这么幸运
So I'm hoping you got the touch.
抱歉  我没感应到什么
I'm sorry, I'm not picking up any vibrations.
或许你把
Well, maybe you would
那小叉子放下以后就能...
if you put down that super tiny fork with the--
这是什么面包
Ooh, what kind of bread is that?
我这不是自助餐  贱人
This ain't no buffet, bitch.
那就给我算命  贱人
Well, then tell me my fortune, bitch.
现在我有感觉了
See, now I'm getting something.
你已经遇到了
You have already met the man
会跟你共度一生的男人
you're going to spend your life with.
是吗  他长什么样
Ooh, I have? What does he look like?
是个外国人
He's the exotic type.
我喜欢外国人
Ooh! I love exotic!
我看见他穿西装打领带
I see him in a suit and tie.
真帅
Oh, he fancy!
再详细点
Tell me more.
他戴领结
He wears a bow tie...
名字开头是字母E
and his name starts with an "E."
没门
Oh, hell no!